let's quickly just try we just want to
have a quick try related to you know um
text track how does it work and here you
go so we are looking to analyze a past
up that is you know your earnings your
salary slip and all of that and you can
see this is a pretty long salary slip
with a lot of information available now
you have one that is the raw text now
this raw text on the right hand side is
basically all the text that um you know
Amazon text track was able to pick up
now let's go to layout so it's saying
that is it has basically laid out the
you know uh page or the document in all
of these sections let's go to forms you
can see any form related data you can go
to tables to see if there was any table
ay um some queries and if there were any
signature says that one signature was
detected over here so there you go you
can see this is how basically it is able
to extract all your data you can see
every single thing is extracted over
here for example it's your in statement
you know um this is the company's name
um it's your your pay perod is between
this date to this date it has couple of
you know text CL you know some pii data
is also available over here and all such
good things so let's go ahead and choose
something else let's take a a health
insurance card for example so this is a
insurance card you can see that we have
the insurance company's name we have
some user details some date related to
the
insurance and all of those things you
can see it was able to detect all of
these raw texts when we click on layout
you can see that these are the layouts
that it has directed you can see the
company's name the person's name with
his member ID um you can see that
effective date dates contract code and
all of that so you can see Amazon textt
track is can basically extract anything
and everything from a document for you